
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<faqs>
<faq><id>1</id>
<title>When can I start the tele-consult call?</title>
<content>
On the Dashboard screen you can view all the tele-consult appointments
Each appointment is booked with an "advance call time" for a doctor to call the patient in advance (e.g. a doctor can call 30 minutes ahead of a scheduled appointment, if agreed to by the patient)
Based on the selected time range for the booked appointments a Start icon is displayed Once the Start icon is enabled on the Dashboard screen, Wellzio offers a 30 minutes "grace period" after the appointment time (this is how long the patient can be late to the appointment by).
When the appointment time exceeds 30 minutes grace time the status gets updated to Missed and the icon will be disabled. The patient will have to call LVP and schedule a separate appointment.
</content>
</faq>
<faq><id>2</id>
<title>How can I start the tele-consult call?</title>
<content>
On the Dashboard screen you can view all the tele-consult appointments
At the scheduled appointment time a blue button gets enabled with Start text
Click on the Start button to initiate the video call with the specified patient.
</content>
</faq>
<faq><id>3</id>
<title>Can I do an Audio-only call?</title>
<content>
Yes, it is possible to do a Audio-only call with a patient
For each patient under Actions column, click on the "3 dots"
Find the Audio Call option
Clicking on Audio Call takes you to Call Patient screen
Click on "Make a call".
</content></faq>
<faq><id>4</id>
<title>How do I see patient history?</title>
<content>
On Dashboard screen, patient details will be displayed for booked appointments
Click on the Patient name
Patient History Chart screen is displayed
Under the history, patient history details will be displayed
History details gets displayed in OVS under medical history and family history.
</content></faq>
<faq><id>5</id>
<title>How do I cancel an appointment?</title>
<content>
On Dashboard screen, patient details will be displayed for booked appointments
For each patient under Actions column, click on the "3 dots"
Select Cancel Appointment
A specific patient appointment can be canceled from the Schedule page by clicking on the Delete icon of a particular patient.
</content></faq>
<faq><id>6</id><title>How do I add a new Physician to Wellzio?</title>
<content>
On the Dashboard screen click on the Settings link displayed next to physician name
Click on theAdministration tab
Select the appropriate Center and Organization from the drop-down list
Under "Add Staff", select the user type from the drop-down list
Enter details
Click on Add icon  
</content></faq>
<faq><id>7</id><title>If patient has poor internet connectivity, how do I switch from Video call to Audio call?</title>
<content>
Switch from video to Audio call by clicking on Call icon displayed next to the patient name in the OVS. 
</content></faq>
<faq><id>8</id><title>How do I enter data in the OVS?</title>
<content>
Prior to entering patient details, Doctor must select "Patient Attended" and "Consent Taken" to Yes.
This puts the OVS in editable mode. After this, the Physician can enter data.
</content>
</faq>
<faq><id>9</id><title>How do I edit a Prescription</title>
<content>
As soon as a call is initiated by the Physician, an OVS screen is displayed
Doctor must select "Patient Attended" and "Consent Taken" to Yes
This puts the OVS in editable mode. After this, the Physician can enter data. To do this:/***/Go to prescription tab to prescribe medication;Click on View Summary;Select one of Pend or Edit the OVS.;In Pend mode, the Physician can revisit the OVS and then finally Submit;Once an OVS is submitted, there is no option to edit the prescription again
</content>
</faq>
<faq><id>10</id><title>How do I edit the prescription after I submitting the visit summary</title>
<content>
Once an OVS is submitted, there is no option to edit the prescription again
</content>
</faq>
<faq><id>11</id><title>How do I upload my digital signature?</title>
<content>
On the Dashboard screen, click on the Settings link displayed next to your name
Click on Accounts
Click Upload Signature button and upload a jpeg/jpg file of your signature.
</content>
</faq>
<faq><id>12</id><title>How do I check the revenue generated for each physician?</title>
<content>
Click on the Analytics tab 
Select Physician's name from drop-down
Select the date range
</content>
</faq>
<faq><id>13</id><title>How do I change my password?</title>
<content>
On the Dashboard screen click on Settings displayed next to your name 
Click on Accounts
Enter current password
Enter new password and confirm new password
Click on Change for updating to new password
</content>
</faq>
<faq><id>14</id><title>How do I change my practice hours?</title>
<content>
On the Dashboard screen click on Settings displayed next to your name 
Click on Organization
Click on Practice Hours
Click Create New
Create New hours page is displayed, select From date and time and To date and time
Click on Create to publish practice hours.
</content>
</faq>
<faq><id>15</id><title>How do I look up appointments for a future date?</title>
<content>
On the Dashboard page
Select date from the date field
List of appointment booked are displayed.
</content>
</faq>
</faqs>
